chalo.pk 2017-12-15

# Privacy Policy - CHALO.PK

### Privacy Policy

Terms and Conditions

Chalo's Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you decide to share, and help you make informed decisions when using Chalo, located at www.chalo.pk and its directly associated domains (collectively, "Chalo" or "Website"). By using or accessing Chalo, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

The Information We Collect

When you visit Chalo you provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by us and Web Site use information collected by us as you interact with our Web Site.

When you register with Chalo, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, your email address, your telephone number, your address, your gender and any other personal or preference information that you provide to us.

When you enter Chalo, we collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all Chalo visitors. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you come back to Chalo. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature.

You post User Content (as defined in the Chalo Terms of Use) on the Site at your own risk. We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that User Content you post on the Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your User Content.

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on Chalo is a violation of the Chalo Terms of Service and should be reported to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

If you choose to use our invitation service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Chalo stores this information to send this one-time email, to register a friend connection if your invitation is accepted, and to track the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) to request that we remove this information from our database.

Children Under Age 13

Chalo does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for Chalo or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on Chalo. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Children Between the Ages of 13 and 18

We recommend that minors over the age of 13 ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.

Use of Information Obtained by Chalo

When you register with Chalo, you create your own profile and privacy settings. Your profile information, as well as your name, email and photo, are displayed to people on Chalo. We may occasionally use your name and email address to send you notifications regarding new services offered by Chalo that we think you may find valuable.

Profile information you submit to Chalo will be available to users of Chalo. Your name, and profile picture thumbnail will be available in search results across Chalo. Chalo may send you service-related announcements from time to time through the general operation of the service. For instance, if a friend sends you a new message , you may receive an email alerting you to that fact. Chalo may use information in your profile without identifying you as an individual to third parties.

Sharing Your Information with Third Parties

We do not provide contact information to third party marketers without your permission. We share your information with third parties only in limited circumstances where we believe such sharing is 1) reasonably necessary to offer the service, 2) legally required or, 3) permitted by you.

When you use Chalo, certain information you post or share with third parties, such as personal information, comments, messages, photos.

This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by Chalo and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers.

Changing or Removing Information

Access and control over most personal information on Chalo is readily available through the profile editing tools. Chalo users may modify or delete any of their profile information at any time by logging into their account. Information will be updated immediately. Individuals who wish to deactivate their Chalo account may do so on the My Account page. Removed information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available to members of Chalo.

Where you make use of the communication features of the service to share information with other individuals on Chalo, however, (e.g., sending a personal message to another Chalo user) you generally cannot remove such communications.

Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions

Your use of Chalo, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Use and all of its dispute resolution provisions including arbitration, limitation on damages and choice of law. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, and material changes will take effect within 30 days of their posting on this site. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy's new effective date. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or through notice on our home page. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
